(Penny:)What is going on?
(Leonard:)Fine, I told
Sheldon that
(Penny:)her apartment's
been finished,
(Leonard:)but then you just said it's not,
(Leonard:)so now I'm all confused.
(Amy:)Penny was just
covering for me.
(Amy:)My place has been
ready for two weeks.
(Sheldon:)How could you lie to me?
(Penny:)Uh, she's enjoyed
living with you.
(Penny:)It's called being in love.
(Leonard:)Mm-hmm, and
what's it called
(Leonard:)when you
secretly get rid
(Leonard:)of all your
husband's stuff?
Wha... That is not true!
Wh-wh-wh... Bernadette
told Howard, Howard told me.
(Leonard:)Plus, I can see
all my stuff is gone!
(Penny:)Oh, so, you believe your friend,
and your friend's wife
(Penny:)and your own eyes over me?
(Penny:)Wow.
(Leonard:)You really didn't
think I'd notice
(Leonard:)my stuff was missing?
(Penny:)Uh, did you notice
your key chain?
Where's Batman?!
(Leonard:)Hey.